Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Moving images and audio recordings
  - Video cassettes
    - Unique
      - Planet rock-Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force, Undated; V-9990; Tommy Boy Records (Box 101)
      - Ndodemnyama (Free South Africa)- Hip Hop Artists Against Apartheid, 1989-10-17; V-9992; U-Matic (Box 101)
      - Shout it out-Afrika Bambaataa, 1988-04-08; V-9996; 0:04:09; VHS (Box 101)
        as labeled
      - "Street dreams" (aka "Rock House"), 1989-03-07; V-9997; VHS (Box 101)
        Movie "Crack House"
      - The recording of "Sun City"-Artists United Against Apartheid, 1985; V-9998; VHS (Box 101)
      - Afrika Bambaataa music videos, 1988; V-10039; VHS (Box 102)
      - Hip Hop on the Capitol: Day 1 B-Boy Supremacy Battle, Sacramento, CA Feb. 14, 1999 Universal Zulu Nation Northstar Chapter; for Mumia Abu-Jamal, Undated; V-7161; VHS (Box 102)
      - Universal Zulu Nation on One World Order, T.C. Islam, Undated; V-7164; VHS (Box 102)
      - Bronx River Under Siege, Undated; V-7168; VHS (Box 102)
      - The 21st Zulu Nation Anniversary, New Yorker Hotel, Nov. 10, 11, 12, 13 1995 Part 2 (Old Dirty Bastard, Supernatural, M.C./D.J. Battle B-Boys, Undated; V-7169; VHS (Box 102)
      - Live in Europe The Lovesexy Tour Featuring Prince, Sheila E, Cat NeverB/4 Release in the U.S.A., Undated; V-7170; VHS (Box 102)
      - Prince -- 4/9/02 Avery Fisher Hall, NYC (AUD) -93 mins-HIFI, Undated; V-7171; VHS (Box 102)
      - "Block Party", Undated; V-7172; VHS (Box 102)
      - 1. Afrika Bambaataa- Zulu Nation on Rap City! Lectures in Houston, Texas 1. Afrika Babaataa- Brother Righteous 2. Dr. Lenord Jeffererys 3. Matubulluka, Undated; V-7173; VHS (Box 102)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Meeting June 2, 1993, Undated; V-7178; VHS (Box 102)
      - Rev. Phil Valentine;Afrika Bambaataa on "Like It Is", Undated; V-7183; VHS (Box 102)
      - MTV's Making the Video: Freestyle Basketball, Undated; V-7184; VHS (Box 102)
      - U.A.M. Presents umoja (unity) forum Oberia Dempsey Center 12/22/1999, Undated; V-7185; VHS (Box 102)
      - Afrika Bambaataa, Alien Ness, San Francisco State University October 24, 2000, Undated; V-7188; VHS (Box 102)
      - 16+ Zulu 11/9/1990, Undated; V-7189; VHS (Box 102)
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Family Liveat the Palace in Paris, France June 25, 1987, Undated; V-7190; VHS (Box 102)
      - Afrika Bambaataa, Helsinki, Finland, July 6, 2000, Undated; V-7191; VHS (Box 102)
      - Million Man March Tues. Aug. 15, 1995 Minister Khallid Abdul Muhammad; Minister Conrad Muhammad;Brother Melechi; T.C. Islam; Brother Prophet, Undated; V-7194; VHS (Box 102)
      - U.A.M. Presents Steve Cokely The Plan: 10 Things You Would Tell Black People Oberia Dempsey Center 5/6/98, Undated; V-7195; VHS (Box 102)
      - The Zulu Nation Rally at City Hall New York, Undated; V-7196; VHS (Box 102)
      - South Bank Show; Zulu Nation, Kanazawa T.V. (Japanese program), Undated; V-7197; VHS (Box 102)
      - Hip Hop Conference in Chicago Feb. 2001, Undated; V-7198; VHS (Box 102)
      - The 23rd Annual Universal Zulu Nation Hip Hop Anniversary, Undated; V-7199; VHS (Box 102)
      - The Hip Hop Years (close to the edge) Part 1, Undated; V-7200; VHS (Box 102)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Meeting Wed. February 5, 1997; Al Hajj, Undated; V-7201; VHS (Box 102)
      - The 20th Annual Universal Zulu Nation Hip Hop Anniversary, Undated; V-7202; VHS (Box 102)
      - Experience Music Project Interview with Afrika Bambaataa and Alien Ness, JBL Theatre, Seattle, WA October 28, 2000, Undated; V-7203; VHS (Box 102)
      - Afrika Bambaataa Live Video D.J. Jam at Beatz n Bobs, in Exeter, England Tues. March 6, 2001, Undated; V-7204; VHS (Box 102)
      - Groove wit' da gingle bells '97: Berlin, Germany, December 27, 1997, 1997-12-27; V-7205; VHS (Box 102)
        Universal Zulu Nation in Berlin, Germany
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Westbam, Undated; V-7206; 0:04:05; Betamax (Box 102)
  - Audio cassettes
    - Unique
      - (unlabeled), 1/4 inch audiotape (Box Box 145)
      - (unlabeled, Maxell Epitaxial XLII, 90 minutes), audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - (unlabeled, TDK AD, 60 minutes), audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - (unlabeled, TDK, 90 minutes), audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - 1) Dance all night -Radio Mix, Screamin' Rachael, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - 16th Zulu Nation Anniversary, 1990-11-09; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - 17th Zulu Nation Anniversary Tape 3, Live Crowd, Biz Marky, KRS-One, Grand Puba & More; Live without mixing board at Club Marquee, 1991-11-10; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - A) In Full; B)In Gear, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa & Family new jams, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa, Cassetta, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa: Clean up your act, Zouk Ya Body, World Racial War, Reckless, Recklessly, Mind Body and Soul, 1988-08; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa: Recklessly (soca mix) [cassette inside may be different recording], 199u-09-08; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - ANC Free South Africa, Bambaataa, Seq. 106, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - At the hype, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Bam (Free South Africa), Sequences, Masters, Hollywood, Nite, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Bam Sea[?] 107.6, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Bam show tape: 1. Rock America; 2. Bionic Kats; 3. Kickout the jams; 4. What time is it, 1986-09-19; 1/4 inch audiotape (Box Box 145)
      - Bambaataa Sounds, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Bambaataa Sounds, & GZ LG, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Bambaataa Sounds, Volume 1, James Brown, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Bambaataa, Max Program, Ultimate Force, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Blank, unopened, "Afrika Bambaataa", 1/4 inch audiotape (Box Box 145)
      - De Mello Music, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - De Music, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - De Point Productions, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - DJs & Mcs (Tape II), The Battle for World Supremacy, New Music Seminar IIX, 1988; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Funkin' Pt. 2, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Hip hop, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Hot Stuff (Bee), It's Hell, Soca, Bam & Kenny Jam, "Tone", Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Hot Stuff, Party, View to a Kill, Fatback Samples - Drum Roll, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - It's Hell, So click to that (Pt. 1), Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - It's Hell, So click to that (Pt. 2), Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Like this 12" vocal, 1986-10-20; 1/4 inch audiotape (Box Box 145)
      - Pt. 2 Hot Stuff, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Right to resist, 1988-12-04; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Right to resist, 1988-12-04; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Shonuff Funky #2, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Show DAT, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Skeff/Poobah, BamSound Part 1, 107.6, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Skeff/Poobah, BamSound Part 2, 107.6, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Snuky Tate, 1987; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Soca Jam, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Sono mondiale, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - St. Ides Commercial, Afrika Bambaataa, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - St. Ides Commercial, Afrika Bambaataa, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - St. Ides Commercial, Afrika Bambaataa "Give Back", DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Sweet Lizard Illtet-M*G*T*- James Brown / Afrika Bambaataa, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - The Jams, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Time Zone Live in Paris, 1987-06-uu; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - To Bam From Jay / Bx River, 1990-03-13; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Universal Zulu Nation at Club Babon, Trouble Funk, Live in O.C., audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Upmost 2 Demo's. 1. Cashualty of love; 2. The child is yours, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - W.A. Valentino and the Keyboard Clan, Gucci girl, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - You don't love me if can't respect me (Part 1) / Tempo 101.6, Sounds Bambaataa, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - You don't love me if can't respect me (Part 2) / Tempo 101.6, Sounds Bambaataa, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - You don't love me if can't respect me [Part 3?] / Tempo 101.6, Sounds Bambaataa, Floppy disk: 5 1/4 inch (Box Box 145)
      - 20th Zulu Nation Ann. Tape #1, 1994-11-11; audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Afrika Bambaaaa and Jazzy Jay #5; Side 2: Touch of class disco/Zulu Nation/Cold Crush/Debbie Dee Wanda Dee, audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Afrika Bambaataa at Viper Room, audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Afrika Bambaataa St. Ides comm., audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Afrika Bambaataa-Techno dance mixes 95, 1995; audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Bam interview in Germany, audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Cold Crush Cosmic Froce, Battle of MC/DJ, #31, audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Hot 97 Old School Throwdown (#8) Live at Paramount, audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Kiss 100FM, Afrika Bambaataa-Givin' it up, audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Live at Barclays, Zulu Nation, 1992-07-31; audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Nick & Afrika Bambaaaa @ Homeless, Dundee, Scotland, 1997-03-22; audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Show: Time Zone, 96 Luserne[sic] "Suisse", audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - The 10th Black History, Feb. 27, 1992, 1992-02-27; audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - WSOU FM New Jersey-Afrika Bambaataa and Rob Booski, 1999-08-23; DAT (Box Box 143)
      - Zulu Nation at Monroe H.S. #21; Zulu Nation at T. Connection, audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Zulu Nation in Italy, audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Zulu Nation, Cosmic Force, Soulsonic Force at the ACE Center, Amityville, LI #20, 1980-12-05; audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Afrika Bambaataa (3), Radio Nova[?], 1987-02-07; audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Bambaataa at Charisma Fashion Show at El Chevere, 1978-12-03; audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Bambaataa I., Brentwood, C.I.[?], audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Bambaataa/Zulu Nation at T. Connection, audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - Nescafe, 1989-09-04; audiocassette (Box Box 143)
      - "Jazzin"-Khayan, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - "The Cooley"-Afrika Bambaataa, 1994-06-01; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - 1. Kid Capri: D-Amazin WBLS; 2. Bam/D-Amazin/Akmed-no music Kid Capri (WBLS); 3. Kiss 100 in London, Max & Dave: IKY-C, D-Amazin; 4. Silver D: WBLS, Bam/IKY-C: no music; 5. Bam & IKY-C: Bug out; 6. Awesome Z. WHBI, Bam & IKYC; 7. Awesome Z, WHBI, Bam/IKY-C "Don't Yell Bam", DAT (Box Box 144)
      - 1FM Friday, 1AM-2:30AM (1 of 2), 1995-10-21; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - 1PM Fri., 21-10-95, 2:30AM-4AM (2 of 2), audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Afrika Bambaataa - Riga '95, CD (Box Box 144)
      - Afrika Bambaataa [tape says: "DJ Mesia: The history of bass"] (from Germany), audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Soulsonic Force: Do the wrong thing; Suffer; Ominous Isthmus; Rock what you got; Ruckus; For what it's worth, DAT (Box Box 144)
      - Afrika Bambaataa and the Soulsonic Force, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Bambaataa and Boogie Brown: Hip Hop tracks for Shaji's Rap Artist, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Bambaataa: Vocal samples, DAT (Box Box 144)
      - D.J. Afrika Bambaataa Live!, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #1: Afrika Bambaataa, Zulu Nation, 1994-11-18; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #10 Afrika Bambaataa/EZ/LG, Fat Friday and True School at Noon, 1995-03-24; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #14 Afrika Bambaataa/EZ/LG, Fat Friday, 1995-04-21; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #15 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Fat fridays, 1994-12-30; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #16 Afrika Bambaataa/EZ/LG, Fat Friday, 1995-01-20; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #16 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Fat fridays, 1995-01-20; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #17 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Fat fridays, 1994-12-29; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #18 Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Zulu Nation, Fat Friday, 1994-11-25; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #2 Afrika Bambaataa, Zulu Nation, Old school at noon, 1994-11-04; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #23 Afrika Bambaataa/EZ/LG, Fat Fridays, 1995-02-24; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #24 Afrika Bambaataa, Fat Friday, 1995-05-12; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #25 [#4?] Afrika Bambaataa with George Clinton, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #27 Afrika Bambaataa/Family, Fat Fridays, 1994-10-21; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #27 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Fat fridays, 1994-10-21; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #28 Afrika Bambaataa/Easy LG, Fat Fridays, 1994-07-23; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #28 Afrika Bambaataa/Easy LG, Fat Fridays, 1994-07-23; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #29 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Fat Joe, Fat Fridays, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #30 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Fat Fridays- Old school at noon, 1994-11-11; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #32 Afrika Bambaataa/Easy L.G., Fat Fridays, Old school at noon, 1994-10-28; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #33 Afrika Bambaataa/ Zulu Nation, Fat Fridays, Old school at noon, 1994-10-08; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #34 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Easy, LG, Old school at noon, electrofunk mix, 1994-12-02; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #35 [#7?] Afrika Bambaataa / Zulu Nation, Jazzy Jay, L.G., 1994-09-02; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #35 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Sat, Sept 3, 199u-09-03; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #36 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Jazzy Jay, LG, 1994-09-03; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #4: Afrika Bambaataa/E.Z.L.G., Zulu Nation, Fat Fridays, 1994-12-09; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #5 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Fat fridays- Old school at noon, electrofunk mix, 1994-08-19; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #5: Afrika Bambaataa/E.Z.L.G., Fat Fridays, 1995-01-06; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #6, 1994-12-16; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #6 Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Fat Fridays, 1994-06-26; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 #7: Afrika Bambaataa Old School at noon, 1994-07-29; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 [box: G.R.A.S.S. (Grass ruts and so speshal[sic])], 1995-03-10; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 [no #] Afrika Bambaataa/LG, Fat Fridays, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 [no#] Afrika Bambaataa/Easy/LG/Zulu Nation, 1995-09-08; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 [no#] Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Xmas show, 1994-12-23; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 [no#] Afrika Bambaataa/Zulu Nation, Xmas show, 1994-12-23; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Hot 97 [no#] Live in concert, 1995-04-14; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - In a minute, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Kingu Remix's Hydraulic Funk; Matrix, Twigy, Time Zone, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Live at the Key, Zulu nation, tape 4, 2000-03-01; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Maurice White Tribute, 2000-03-10; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Music for Planet Rock label, DAT (Box Box 144)
      - Old School at Noon-Black History, 97.1, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Planet Rock 2, DAT (Box Box 144)
      - Sample clearance request from Parlophone, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Space Funk Freestyle, KPFA, History of Funk, 2000-09-08; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Time Zone, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Time Zone, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #1, Hot 97, Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #10, Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #11 Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #12 Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #14, Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #15 Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #16 Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #17 Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #18 Zulu nation, Hot 97, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #19 Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #2, Hot 97, Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #20 Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #3, Hot 97, 1995-03-17; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #3, Hot 97, Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #4, Hot 97, Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #5 Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #6, Hot 97, Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #7 Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #8, Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School at Noon #9 Zulu nation, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - True School, Afrika Bambaataa, 1995-06-23; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - WHCR 90.3, True School Radio, 2004-03-25; Mini Disc (Box Box 144)
      - X Bambaataa-De Point, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Zulu Nation: Globe Dazazin, DAT (Box Box 144)
      - (unlabeled, TDK, D90), audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - 16th Zulu Nation Anniversary (Part 3), 1990-11-09; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - 16th Zulu Nation Anniversary (Part 3), 1990-11-11; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - 16th Zulu Nation Anniversary: Brand Nubians, Lord Finess, Jungle Bros, KRS One, Dougie Fresh, 1990-11-11; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - 17th Zulu Nation Anniversary, 1991-11-10; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - 17th Zulu Nation Anniversary (Part 1): Non-stop dance and Lovebug Starski, 1991-11-10; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Demo cuts: We came to rock, Clevelands my house, A situation (written, produced, performed by Jeffrey Scot, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Nigeria-Abana-African Spiritual, Adofo - Jin-Go-Lo-Ba, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Rehersel[sic] tape, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Soulsonic Force Beats, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Zulu Nation Anniversary [16th], 1990-11-09; audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - Zulu Nation in Frankfurt, Germany, audiocassette (Box Box 144)
      - "Feel the Vibe": Khayan by Afrika Bambaataa, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - "Oskoorland" Radio Campus 107.2FM, Afrika Bambaataa, 1997-12-05; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - "Pupunanny": Afrika Bambaataa, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - [no label], DAT (Box Box 145)
      - 1. Boom Blasters D.J. Siten; 2. Bad, Mad & Wicked; Indian dance music #6, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - 1. Hey Jude (rap); 2. Hey Jude (vox); 3. You ask for the moon; 4. Hey Jude (1994); 5. Rock session; 6. The look in your eyes; 7. I'm ok, you're ok; 8. Got to give up, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - A Natural Man, NIG records, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - AB & DR (1), DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa "The Cooley", 1994-06-02; DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force, Planet Rock & Lost Generation The Album (master tape), audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force: 1)Lost Generation; 2)Bang Bang; 3)Sex is the best, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Family, Live in Tokyo, on air Sibuya [Shibuya?], 1992-04-17; DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Hody Hard[???] "TechnoElectro", DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa and the Soulsonic Force [Shimizu Album Jap], audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa presents Hip Hop/Funk/Dance Classics: Trouble Funk Live, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa radio songs, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa, Soulsonic Force, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa: Intro; Hell below; Feeling irie; Get up and dance; Can't give you up; Feel the vibe; Pupunanny; Soca fever; Electro funk express, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa: The No Nonsense Song; This is Time Zone; You're the One; It's a B-Boy Thang; Jazzin', DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Afrika Bambaataa's crazy tape for Poochie, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Bam songs-Universal Future Funk: It's Sly Stone; Life & Deat in G&A; Reduction; Give peace a chance; Don't bust the pusher; Fiction; Fight the power Inst., DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Bambaataa demos '94 (2), 1994; DAT (Box Box 145)
      - CDLD; I'm The Man; Plumbers In The House, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - D.J. Fashion Party Mix, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - D.J. Mesia, Zulu Berlin: Wild Style Project, Out of time, Future planet, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Demo[?] X, Afrika Bambaataa, 1997-07-16; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - DMC mix, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Extra Hot 5 by Amit & San J; Bhangra Fever; Indian dance music #8, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Fast Changing Jams, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Feel the Vibe by Khayan (Mix A & B), 1996-11; DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Flatbush Zulu Various Artists, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - For "Bam Live": Motocompohead & 2 Minutes of Fuk, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Go go funk #1, Afrika Bambaaaa, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Happy, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Indian dance music #10, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Indian dance music #4, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Interview with Afrika Bambaataa w/Christie Z. Pabon, Complete Bronx Soundwalk, 2003, CD (Box Box 145)
      - Italian Zulu song for Time Zone, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Live in Japan, D.J. gig '99, 1999; DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Mind Control, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Music for Planet Rock label, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Planet Rock, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Planet Rock, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Planet Rock 2 A/B: 1. Burn; 2. Say it loud; 3. You're the one; 4. The Nononsense song; 5. Sweat; 6. This is Time Zone; 7. Miss Lottie Dottie; 8. Ndodemnyama; 9. Save the world, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Plant Rock-D.J. Fashion remix, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Pupunanny: by A. Bambaataa, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Quality - Demo, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Return to Planet Rock/Planet Rock Acid Mix, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Sex, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Tape 1: The Zulu Shout Out (Pt. 1&2); Tape 2: Watch Me Now, Accappellaaaaa, Zulu War Chant Fashion, 1992-03-10; DAT (Box Box 145)
      - The Cooley, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - The Godfather Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Soulslinger, Zulu 1555, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - The Next Diffusion: Down with da Nation (Writing on box: Cannavo Maurizio, V. Mirafiori 21/E, 10092, Beinasco (Torino) Italy), DAT (Box Box 145)
      - The Planet Rock Album, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Thy will "B" funk, 1999, Afrika Bambaataa and Time Zone, 1999 Master cassette, 1999; audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Time Zone C & D, audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Time Zone: Funk Dat, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Time Zone: Throw Ya Funky Hands Up (CD Single), CD (Box Box 145)
      - True School Radio, Mini Disc (Box Box 145)
      - Y2K Beats-Time Zone, Bambaataa, L.G., audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Zulu 2000, DAT (Box Box 145)
      - Zulu Internet Info, Zip Disc (Box Box 145)